TARCHANA

TRAINER

<u>Detailed Resume</u>



ABOUT ME

I am a creative. My interests brought my hands-on experience in various fields. Some of the major fields are in customer service, technical service, human resource management, trainer and resolution provider, and societal dynamics to further enhance my skills in various dimensions.

WORK EXPERIENCE

► PLANET SPARK

Jan 2023 - Nov 2023

PUBLIC SPEAKER Trainer

Officially recruited as a trainer but due to advanced dashboard automation, in reality, I started guiding friends technically as a teacher and also learning for myself from them. Its a remote job.

► CSR - REDINGTON Placement & Jul 2019 - Aug 2020 technical trainer

Empower students with employment opportunities, make them skillful; personality development, technical training like coding, non-technical, like aptitude etc.; the rest of the roles are based on creating employment opportunities and CSR empowerment of village and student development initiatives with student support.

VITA INSTITUTE 2018

TRAINEE for trainer position

► HOME TUTIONS Mar 2015 - Sept 2016 School students teacher (KG-dyslexia, 2nd, 3rd 4th, 9th,10th std. Stud.)

OTHER EXPERIENCES

Intern Python Developer, Now **Techinterex**

Trainee for Full Stack dev., Now Yaazli Techy Groups

Website designing, 2024 **Mewalla Consultancy services**

Counselor - Cust. Support,2023 SARVM.AI System Pvt. Ltd.

Educational Counselor,2023 Lead IAS Junior Academy HR Executive,2016

EMAAR Services Pvt. Ltd.

Event Manager, 2014

Moon Event Mgt. Services

Technical support executive,2014
SITEL, Tidel Park

Temporary educ. counselor, 2013 **IIHT Institute**

Electrical Trainee, 2011

Arun Rega Bakery & Machineries Pvt. Ltd.

EDUCATION

UG. B.E. – ECE ANNA UNIVERSITY, TIRUNELVELI 2007–2011

PG.DIPLOMA - Embedded VLSI Systems design NIELIT 2012-2013

CONTACT

- +91-9969166913
- techarchie3@gmail.com / arcarchjob@gmail.com
- https://arcarch4.github.io/ portfolio1/
- Chettikulam, Tirunelveli, Tamilnadu

HOBBIES

- Public Speaking
- Resolver
- ▶ Business Comm. Skills
- Exploring/Knowing new things
- Coding /developing stuffs
- Video Making/Editing
- Story Writing
- Multilingual
- Training/ Teaching
- Workshop(eg:-EPFO govt. firm)